(Mrs Cooper:)Shelly! Dinner's ready!
SHELDON: Coming!
(Mrs Cooper:)No cats!
(Penny:)Aw...
(Sheldon:)What is she doing here?
(Mrs Cooper:)I called her.
(Amy:)Your mother thinks
(Amy:)you might be losing
your mind over me.
(Amy:)As a neurobiologist, I was curious.
(Sheldon:)Well, rest assured, I am in
full possession of my faculties.
(sneezes): 25 cats!
(Mrs Cooper:)Oh, God bless you, dear.
(Mrs Cooper:)Sheldon, sit down. Let's talk.
(Sheldon:)All right, but you're
not fooling me.
(Sheldon:)Whenever you say we have to talk,
(Sheldon:)it means you want me to listen.
(Mrs Cooper:)Then stop talking.
(Sheldon:)Yes, ma'am.
(Mrs Cooper:)Now, the reason I
called Amy over was
(Mrs Cooper:)to find out what type
of person she is.
(Mrs Cooper:)And after chatting a bit,
(Mrs Cooper:)I have to say that while she is a
perfectly unique young woman,
(Mrs Cooper:)you two are definitely not
suited for each other.
(Sheldon:)That's a peculiar conclusion.